animaxtv.com 2007-06-29

# Sony Pictures - Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT AND THE WEB SITE TERMS OF SERVICE.

**_Notice_**

This Web site is operated by Sony Pictures Entertainment Inc. and/or its subsidiary companies in the United States of America (collectively, “SPE”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to information that you provide to SPE via this site, and/or by use of other services (collectively, the “Services”) that may be provided by other means or media, including as set forth below and as defined in the applicable Terms of Service or other terms. 

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you notice of SPE’s information management practices, including the types of information gathered, how it is used and safeguarded, and the degree to which you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information. Your use of any SPE Service or Web site constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms. The [Terms of Service](http://www.sonypictures.com/corp/tos.html) for this Web site are hereby incorporated by reference. 

**_Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect_**

SPE respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personally identifiable information that you provide in connection with your use of its Web sites and Services. 

_E-mail Newsletter Subscriptions_

To subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, you will need to provide your e-mail address. You may also be asked for other information when you subscribe. 

_User Accounts_

In order to use our chat rooms, message boards, and certain other Services, you will need to register and create a user account ("User Account"). There is no cost to create a User Account in most cases. You may be asked to choose a user name, screen name, or member name (each, a "User Name") and password. Please do not use your real name or the real name of another person when selecting a User Name. You will also be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information and other information about yourself, such as your first and last name, date of birth, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.

Please note that your User Name will be available to the Internet's general public while you participate in some Services, like chat rooms or message boards, so you should exercise discretion when using these Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in such Services. In some instances, you may choose to create a "Public Profile" that will be available to others on the Internet. Public Profiles are managed entirely by you, and you are solely responsible for your Public Profile's content and its "public" or "private" status. You are also responsible for maintaining and updating the registration information in your User Account with current and complete information. You may access, edit or remove your Public Profile by signing in to your User Account and following the directions there. You can also send an e-mail to [SonyPrivacy@sonypictures.com](mailto:SonyPrivacy@sonypictures.com) to request deactivation of your User Account. 

_**__**Special Promotions and Purchases_

To participate in some Services such as sweepstakes, contests and surveys ("Special Promotions"), or to make online purchases ("Purchases"), you will need to provide personally identifiable information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, and date of birth. Your information may be collected by SPE or by a third party, such as a co-sponsor or a vendor involved in, or providing services in connection with, a Special Promotion, or an e-commerce partner in the case of a Purchase (e.g., www.SonyStyle.com or www.yahoo.com).

If you make a Purchase or enter a sweepstakes or other Special Promotion on one of our sites or through our Services, SPE will collect your personally identifiable information, and you are deemed to consent to us providing your information to third parties who provide certain services such as processing of credit card transactions, customer service, promotion or sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable. (As more fully described below in Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information \- Personally Identifiable Information, these third parties are prohibited from using this information for their own marketing purposes and/or from sharing, selling, or otherwise distributing any personal data of our customers, unless you choose to opt in for such additional uses and/or disclosure by the third parties, under their respective privacy policies.)

If you make a purchase or enter a promotion (such as a sweepstakes) in which SPE is participating on a third party's Web site (or through some other means or medium), we will collect your information from the third party only if you opt-in to receive additional communications from us, or we are required to fulfill some function in relation to your activity (e.g., to send your order or deliver a prize). 

_Information Collected by Other Means or Media_

In some situations, we may also collect personally identifiable information and other information about you through other means, directly or indirectly. For example, if you access any SPE content, or purchase such content via your wireless carrier or through another third party, SPE may collect information directly from you or through the third party. Likewise, if you use our software, or provide information to other companies who share information about their customers, we may collect additional information about you. In each of these cases, SPE will apply this policy to any personally identifiable information. 

_Information About Other People_

Some SPE sites and Services may ask you to submit personally identifiable information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and other personally identifiable information if you purchase a gift and want to have it sent directly to the recipient. A record of that transaction will be maintained as allowed and/or required by law. 

_Customer Service_

Some Services may offer support and technical assistance through customer service centers via telephone, online chat, or e-mail. Whenever you communicate with customer service, you do so with the understanding that an operator may view and make changes to the information in your User Account in order to provide the assistance that you need. 

**_Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect_**

As part of the registration process for some Services, you may be asked to provide information that does not personally identify you. For example, you may be asked to provide information concerning your film, music or other entertainment preferences, purchasing habits, and the like. This information is generally optional but may be included in your User Account profile. SPE requests this information to understand you better and to also bring to your attention new services, programs, or offers that may be of interest to you. 

In many cases, SPE will automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of its sites and Services. SPE might collect, among other things, information concerning the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your "click path" through the SPE sites or "click-through" from an e-mail, the Web site or advertisement that was linked to or from the SPE site when you visited, and your IP address. To do this, SPE may use cookies and other technology (see below). If you are using our wireless Services, we may also automatically collect information such as the type of wireless device you are using, your mobile identification number (assigned by your telecommunications carrier) and telecommunications carrier. Your use of our Web sites and Services, and information provided through these technologies, will be anonymous unless you provide us with personally identifiable information or have provided such information in the past. 

**_Cookies and Related Technology_**

SPE Web sites, and some Services and advertisements may contain "cookies," clear gifs (also known as web beacons or web bugs), or similar technology. A cookie is a piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser, which will store the cookie on your computer if your browser is enabled to accept cookies. Web beacons assist in the delivery of cookies and the collection of non-personally identifiable information, such as "click path" and other data as described above. 

SPE uses cookies, clear gifs, frames, server log analysis and other technologies as they are developed to customize your experience with our sites and Services. 

Most Internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions or "Help" screen to learn more about how to manage cookies. Please note, however, that if you block cookies, some portions of the SPE Web sites and Services may not function properly. 

SPE does not control cookies in third party ads, and visitors are encouraged to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. The ads appearing on our Web sites may be delivered to you by third-party advertising companies. SPE's Privacy Policy does not cover the use of information collected from you by third party ad servers. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**_Special Notice Regarding Children Under 13_**

SPE recognizes the sensitivity of personally identifiable information concerning children under the age of 13 and therefore provides this special notice. SPE is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations regarding children, including the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). Except in limited circumstances allowed by COPPA, SPE will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personally identifiable information from a child under 13 without first obtaining consent from that child's parent or legal guardian. 

If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13, and your child would like to participate in certain Services for which COPPA requires your consent (and SPE has chosen to make such Services available to children in this age group), your child will be prompted to print out a form for you to complete and mail in to SPE. The form will list the information required from both parent/guardian and child, as well as the intended uses of the information. SPE will only collect information that is reasonably necessary for your child to participate, and SPE will not share your child's personally identifiable information with any third party (except for purposes of fulfillment by a third party that has agreed to protect the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy), unless you specifically consent, or as permitted by COPPA or other applicable law. You may also subsequently revoke your consent and request that your child's information be removed from SPE's active list. Please refer to the form for instructions and further information. 

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child under the age of 13 has submitted his or her personally identifiable information without your permission or consent, SPE will make reasonable efforts to remove the information from its active list, at your request. To request the removal of your child's information, please send an e-mail to [SonyPrivacy@sonypictures.com](mailto:SonyPrivacy@sonypictures.com) and be sure to include in your message the same User Name and password and/or e-mail address that your child submitted. 

SPE encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the SPE Web sites and the Internet generally.

**_Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information_**

 _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

From time to time, SPE may use and share with third parties aggregate, non-personally identifiable user information to show general demographic and preference information among users of the SPE Web sites. 

_****Personally Identifiable Information_

SPE uses information about you to deliver the Services that you request, to keep you informed about changes affecting our Services or your account, to inform you of other Services or offers in which you might be interested, and to improve and enhance our sites and Services. If you provide SPE with personally identifiable information, we will take all reasonable and appropriate steps to protect it from unauthorized disclosure. 

If you opt in to receive e-mail from us, you can always opt out of future marketing messages by following the directions in each message to "unsubscribe." However, if you choose to opt out of marketing messages, we reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status, technical support, product information, changes to account terms, and any other matter that might affect our service to you and/or any products you purchased from us or registered with us, as applicable. 

As stated in the Terms of Service, you will be deemed to have consented to the disclosure to, and use by, a subsequent owner or operator of a SPE Web site or Service, of any information about you contained in the applicable SPE database, if SPE or one of its companies assigns its rights and obligations regarding any of your information at the time of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of SPE's or such SPE company's assets related to the applicable site or Service to a subsequent owner or operator. In the event of such a merger, acquisition, or sale, your continued use of the site or any related Service signifies your agreement to be bound by the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy of the site's or Service's subsequent owner or operator. 

The SPE companies may work together in order to provide portions of the SPE sites and some Services (e.g., to fulfill prizes won in a sweepstakes, or to provide other support for a Service). These companies will handle your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

As stated above in **Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect** \- Special Promotions and Purchases, SPE may also work with third parties to provide some Services on our sites. In connection with those Services, you are deemed to consent to us sharing your information with third parties who provide services such as processing of credit card transactions, customer service, promotion administration, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable. Third parties who provide, or participate in, Services on SPE sites are prohibited from using our customers' personally identifiable information for marketing purposes and/or from sharing, selling, or otherwise using such information, unless you choose to opt in to marketing, sharing, or other uses by the third parties. **If you do not want your information to be used for marketing (or other purposes unrelated to the provision of SPE Services) by a third party who participates in a Service on one of our sites, do not opt in to such use by that third party when you register to participate in the Service.**

Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

SPE will not share, sell, rent, or disclose any personally identifiable information that we have collected except as stated herein, or in the following instances: 1) we have been given your consent to disclose; 2) we have previously informed you of the disclosure, including by means of our Privacy Policy or on the Web site, or through the Service where you provided your information; 3) we are required by law, legal process, or court order to disclose; 4) disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may cause or be causing harm to, or interference with, SPE's rights or property, other SPE Web site users, or anyone else; or 5) to respond to an inquiry, request or complaint that you have made. SPE may also use IP addresses in cooperation with Internet service providers to identify users if we deem it necessary to comply with law, to enforce compliance with this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service, or to protect our sites, customers, or others.

**_Our Commitment to Data Security_**

While SPE takes reasonable and appropriate precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized disclosure and to prevent possible security breaches in our Web sites, Services, and customer databases, no Web site, Internet transmission, computer system, or wireless connection is completely secure. Consequently, SPE cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. Your use of the SPE sites and Services is at your own risk. SPE urges you to take steps to keep your information safe by memorizing your password or keeping it in a safe place (separate from your account information), logging out of your User Account, and closing your Web browser. 

Whenever you give SPE sensitive or confidential information (for example, credit card numbers for Purchases), SPE will take commercially reasonable steps to protect the information by establishing a secure connection with your Web browser. SPE employs a security technology known as a secure-socket-layer ("SSL") to protect the transmission of payment information to the site. Unless otherwise specified herein or on the site where you make a Purchase, credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes.

**_Hyperlinks To and From Other Sites_**

SPE sites may frame, and/or contain links to, or advertisements about, non-SPE Web sites. Other sites may also reference, advertise, or link to SPE sites. SPE does not endorse or sponsor other Web sites, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of non-SPE sites, expressly disclaims any statements or assertions made on such Web sites, and denies all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other sites and advertisements. 

**_Consent to Processing in the United States_**

By providing any personally identifiable information to SPE, all users, including, without limitation, users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America. 

**_Contact Us Regarding Privacy_**

SPE is dedicated to protecting your personally identifiable information and welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. You may e-mail your questions or comments to:

**_Notification of Changes_**

SPE reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Service at any time. In case of any material change to the Privacy Policy, we will replace the "Privacy Policy" link on the home page of our sites with a link entitled "Updated Privacy Policy" for no less than 30 days. All changes to the Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Service will be effective when posted, and your continued use of any SPE site or Service after the posting will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

**Effective Date: January 1, 2005**

|
